Guide to the Center for American Music Photos CAM.PHOTOS.2017
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Center for American Music Photos
1830-2017
ULS Archives & Special Collections
CAM.PHOTOS.2017
8 Linear Feet
Music -- United States -- 20th century; Music -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Music -- Pennsylvania; Music -- Manuscripts; Minstrel music -- United States; Foster family; Foster, Morrison, 1823-1904; Foster, Stephen Collins, 1826-1864; Foster, William B., 1779-1855; Stephen Collins Foster Memorial (University of Pittsburgh).
- "Uncle Ned" sheet music cover, British edition (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 1)
  Scope and Content Notes
  Title page of Foster's "Uncle Ned a Favorite American Song" arranged by W. Wilson, London Edition
- "Camptown Races" sheet music cover (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 4)
  Title Page of F.D. Benteen, Baltimore, "Camptown Races"
- "Oh Susanna" sheet music Cover (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 7)
  Title page of Foster's "Oh Susanna" published by John Mitchell, London
- "New Costume Polka" sheet music cover (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 11)
- "The Duet," from Godey's Ladies Book, 1863 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 13)
  Sketch entitled "The Duet" from Godey's Ladies Book. This image appeared in February 1863 issue of Godey's (call number AP2 F182).
- Music of the Ethiopian Serenaders (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 14)
- "Oh Susanna" sheet music cover (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 15)
  Title page of Charles Holt Jr. "Oh Susanna"
- "Susanna Don't You Cry" sheet music cover (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 16)
  title page of "Susanna Don't You Cry" British edition
- "Uncle Ned" sheet music cover (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 17)
  Title page of F.D. Benteen "Uncle Ned"
- Three unidentified people (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 18.01)
  Not in photo index.
- Four unidentified people (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 18.02)
- Unidentified man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 18.03)
- "Oh Susanna Don't You Cry For Me" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 19)
  Title page of "O Susanna Don't You Cry For Me" published by H. Tolkien, London
- "Military Quadrille" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 24)
  Title page of "Military Quadrille" by Robert Stoepel
- Ordway Hall Broadside, May 14, 1855 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 28)
  Poster of Christy Minstrels performing at Ordway Hall May 14, 1855
- Sheet Music cover for "Tramp, Tramp, Tramp", 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 29)
  Title page of George Frederick Root's "Tramp! Tramp! Tramp!", pub. By Root & Cady, 1854
- Sheet music cover for "Nelly Bly", 1850 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 30)
  Title page of Foster's "Nelly Bly" published by Firth, Pond, NY, 1850
- Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 32)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Conductor's Score, zoom on signatures (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32a)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Conductor's score page 1 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32b)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Conductor's score page 2 & 3 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32c)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Conductor's score page 2 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32d)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Conductor's score (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32e)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" conductor's score, zoom on chorus (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32f)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" 1st flute (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32g)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" 2nd flute (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32h)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" 1st clarinet (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32i)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" 2nd clarinette (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32j)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Faggott 1st (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32k)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Faggott 2nd (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32l)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Corno 1st (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32m)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Corno 2nd (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32n)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Tromba 1st (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32o)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Tromba 2nd (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32p)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Tympani (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32q)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" 1st Violin (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32r)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" 1st violin (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32s)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" 2nd violin (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32t)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" 2nd violina (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32u)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" 2nd violina (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32v)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Violino 2 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32w)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Viola (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32x)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Cello (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32y)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Cello (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32z)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Basso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32aa)
  - Manuscript and Parts for Dvorak's arrangement of "Old Folks at Home" Basso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 32bb)
- Alexander Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 33)
  Framed locket of small painted portrait of Alexander Foster
- Alexander Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 34)
- Alexander Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 35)
  Framed locket of small painted portrait of Alexander Foster (close up, no frame)
- Alexander Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 36)
  Framed locket of small painted portrait of Alexander Foster (close up, with frame)
- Alexander Foster and his wife (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 37)
  Small framed painting of Alexander Foster's (unidentified) wife (close up, with frame)
- Alexander Foster and his wife (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 38)
  Small framed painting of Alexander Foster's (unidentified) wife (close up, without frame)
- Alexander Foster's twin daughters (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 39)
  Small framed painting of Alexander Foster's twin daughters
- Alexander Foster's twin daughters (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 40)
  Small framed painting of Alexander Foster's twin daughters (close-up)
- Alexander Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 41)
  Small framed painting of unidentified Foster relative
- Alexander Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 42)
  Small framed painting of unidentified Foster relative (close-up)
- Letter describing Foster lineage, 1843 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 43)
  Page one of an 1843 letter describing Alexander Foster's lineage
- Letter describing Foster lineage, page 2, 1843 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 44)
  Page two of an 1843 letter describing Alexander Foster's lineage
- Letter describing Foster lineage, page 3, 1843 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 45)
  Page three of an 1843 letter describing Alexander Foster's lineage
- Letter describing Foster lineage, page 4, 1843 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 46)
  Page four of an 1843 letter describing Alexander Foster's lineage
- Stained glass windows of "Camptown Races" and "Oh Susanna" in the Stephen Foster Memorial (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 47)
  Stained glass windows of "Camptown Races" and "Oh Susanna" in the Stephen Foster Memorial (black and white)
- Deane Root and Jim Burke photographing Stephen Foster's sketchbook (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 48)
- Deane Root (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 49)
  Deane Root standing beside the historical marker outside the Stephen Foster Memorial
- Deane Root, 1995 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 50)
  Dale Cockrell presents a gavel plaque in recognition of Deane Root's service as Sonneck Society president at the Madison, WI, conference, 1995.
- Painting of Dunning McNair Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 51)
  Painting of Dunning McNair Foster, Stephen Collins's brother.
- Florida Governor Warren Fuller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 52)
  Florida Governor Warren Fuller and unidentified man.
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 53)
  Fletcher Hodges, Jr., speaking at an unidentified event.
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 54)
  Fletcher Hodges, Jr., speaking at White Springs, FL.
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 55)
  Fletcher Hodges, Jr. and an unidentified man at a Foster statue unveiling
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 56)
  Fletcher Hodges, Jr., and three unidentified men seated at an event
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 57)
  Fletcher Hodges, Jr., speaking at Folk Festival
- Evelyn Foster Morneweck seated at a desk (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 58)
  Evelyn Foster Morneweck seated at a Stephen Foster's alleged desk in White Springs, Florida.
- Unidentified young man holding a dog (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 58.01)
  Image is not in photo index.
- Evelyn and Alfred Morneweck (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 59)
  Evelyn Foster Morneweck and husband, Alfred C. Morneweck, at Stephen Foster's alleged desk in White Springs, FL.
- John Tasker Howard and Evelyn Foster Morneweck (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 60)
- Evelyn Foster Morneweck, Alfred C. Morneweck, and Fletcher Hodges Jr. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 61)
- Evelyn Foster Morneweck, Alfred C. Morneweck, Fletcher Hodges Jr., and an unidentified woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 62)
- Jessie Rose Welch seated with Phil Gains, Fletcher Hodges and an unidentified man speaking at the White Springs, Florida, opening ceremonies (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 63)
- Jessie Rose Welch (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 64)
  Jessie Rose Welch seated at the White Springs opening ceremonies
- Jessie Rose Welch (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 65)
  Jessie Rose Welch, speaking at the White Springs opening ceremonies
- Jessie Rose Welch seated with Governor Warner Fuller, Phil Gains, and Fletcher Hodges with Carl Brown speaking (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 66)
- Jessie Rose Welch cutting ribbon with two unidentified women the White Springs opening ceremonies (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 67)
- Jessie Rose Welch, Fletcher Hodges Jr. and an unidentified woman at an event in Florida (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 68)
- An unidentified vocalist performing at an event in Florida (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 69)
- An unidentified vocalist performing at an event in Florida (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 70)
- Unidentified man and an unidentified vocalist in White Springs, FL (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 71)
- White Springs, FL, Foster Museum, 1950 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 72)
  - Stephen Foster Museum in White Springs, Florida, July 29, 1950 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 72a)
  - Stephen Foster Museum in White Springs, Florida, July 29, 1950 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 72b)
- White Springs, FL, museum dedication ceremonies (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 73)
- White Springs, FL, museum dedication ceremonies (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 74)
- White Springs, FL, museum dedication ceremonies (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 75)
- Steuben glass "Stephen Foster" bowl (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 76)
- Proof sheet of photos of Stephen Foster's flute (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 77)
- Side by side images of the gold medal presented to J.K. Lilly in appreciation of his gift of the collection (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 78)
- Handwritten message from Stephen Foster to Martha A. Morse (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 79)
- Address (envelope?) of the handwritten message from Stephen Foster to Martha A. Morse (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 80)
- Front and address (envelope?) of the handwritten message from Stephen Foster to Martha A. Morse (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 81)
- Black back of the handwritten message from Stephen Foster to Martha A. Morse (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 82)
- Piano, flute, and flageolet used by Stephen Collins Foster (possibly at Foster Memorial Home?) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 83)
- Foster's piano in the Stephen Foster Memorial Museum (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 84)
  On loan from the Carnegie Museum
- M.J. Popovich, artist, and his wood in laid portrait of Foster and others (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 85)
- Alexander Foster, cousin of Stephen Foster and Chief Engineer (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 86)
- Birdie Foster, Henry Foster's daughter, 1866 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 87)
- Painting of Stephen Foster's mother, Eliza Clayland Tomlinson Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 88)
- Evelyn Foster Morneweck, as a young woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 89)
- Marion Foster Welsh; Dallas Clayland Rose; Dorothy Jane Rose on the steps of the Foster Memorial home in Lawrenceville, August 1916 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 90)
- Marion Foster Welsh, Jessie Rose and Dallas Rose on the steps of the Foster Memorial Home in Lawrenceville, 1923 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 91)
- Brooch (locket) containing a lock of Marion Foster's hair (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 92)
- Marion Foster Welsh on the steps of the Foster Memorial Home in Lawrenceville, 1923 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 93)
- Marion Foster Welsh as a young woman (tinted photo) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 94)
- Evelyn Louise Foster, daughter of Morrison Foster and his first wife, Jessie Lightner Foster, 1865 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 95)
- Evelyn Louise Foster and her father, Morrison Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 96)
- Evelyn Louise Foster and her father Morrison Foster, 1965 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 97)
- Marion Foster Welsh as an old woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 98)
- Morrison Foster and his wife, Rebecca S. Foster, at Olver Place, Edgeworth, Pa (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 99)
- Sarah Elizabeth "Sally" Foster at 9 months old, April 5, 1934 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 100)
- Painting of a young boy at one time believed to be Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 101)
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr., original curator of the Memorial (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 102)
- William Barclay Foster, son of Morrison & Rebecca S. Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 103)
- William Cogswell painting of William Barclay Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 104)
- Henry Kleber (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 105)
- Augustus A. Adams (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 106)
- Frank Barbeau, half-brother of Pearl Johnson (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 107)
- William Bigler, John Bigler and Washington Bigler (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 108)
- J. Gordon Boggs & Stuart Boggs at the Foster Memorial Home, Lawrenceville, 1923 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 109)
- Anna S. Boggs at the door of the Foster Memorial Home, Lawrenceville, 1923 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 110)
- Mary Wick Crosman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 111)
- Henrietta Crosman as Rosalind in As You Like It (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 112)
- Portrait of Stephen Foster by Thomas S. Cummings, 1853 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 113)
- Mary Thornton Dodge, grandniece of Stephen Foster and granddaughter of Henrietta Wick Thorton (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 114)
- Mary Thornton Dodge, grandniece of Stephen Foster and granddaughter of Henrietta Wick Thornton (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 115)
- Daniel Decatur Emmett's gravestone (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 116)
- Daniel Decatur Emmett as an old man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 117)
- Daniel Decatur Emmett a young man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 118)
- Manuscript of Daniel Decatur Emmett's "Dixie", 1859 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 119)
- Greenfield Village: The house Ford took to Detroit as "Stephen Foster's birthplace" with various Foster relatives (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 120)
  - Greenfield Village: July 4th dedication of "Foster House", 1935 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120a)
  - Greenfield Village: Henry Ford standing in front of "Foster House", 1935 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120b)
  - Greenfield Village: Mrs. Rose (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120c)
  - Greenfield Village: visitors in Mrs. Ford's rose garden (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 120d)
  - Greenfield Village: Mrs. Dallas Rose, Dorothy Rose, and Dallas Rose, Jr., on the steps of the "Foster House" Greenfield Village (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120e)
  - Greenfield Village: Crowd gathered outside the "Foster Home" in Greenfield Village (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 120f)
  - Greenfield Village: people gathered outside of the "Foster Home" at Greenfield Village (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120g)
  - Greenfield Village: Mrs. Rose, granddaughter of Stephen Foster, in the glen at the Henry Ford House and memorial (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120h)
  - Greenfield Village: Mrs. Ford's rose garden (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120i)
  - Greenfield Village: people gathered outside "Foster Home" in Greenfield Village, 1935 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120j)
  - Greenfield Village: Mrs. Dallas Rose at the dedication of Stephen Foster house at Greenfield Village, 1935 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120k)
  - Greenfield Village: Mrs. Henry Ford's rose garden, 1935 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120l)
  - Greenfield Village: Mr. Henry Ford in the doorway of the Foster Home, 1935 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120m)
  - Greenfield Village: Ford House with garden in foreground (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120n)
  - Greenfield Village: Group gathered in front of Ford house (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120o)
  - Greenfield Village: Lillian and ? in Mrs. Ford's Rose garden (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120p)
  - Greenfield Village: unidentified group standing in front of white columned building (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 00120q)
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr., and H. Marie Dermitt at the Foster statue in Schenley Park, March 1937 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 121)
- Side by side images of Josiah Lilly and Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 122)
- Edward MacDowell (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 123)
- Evelyn Foster Morneweck, inscribed to J.K. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 124)
- "Old Black Joe" circa 1932, a slave at the Rowan's Federal Hill (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 125)
- Portrait of Susan Pentland, 1858 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 126)
- James. H. Park presenter of the Foster Memorial Home site, 1914 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 127)
- John W. Robinson of Pittsburgh, son of Andrew L. Robinson & Susan Pentland (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 128)
- Mrs. C.M. Redman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 129)
- Mrs. C.M. Redman with a portrait of James Barclay, 1941 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 130)
- Mrs. C.M. Redman at "Barclay Manor", 1941 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 131)
- Mrs. C.M. Redman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 132)
- Deane L. Root, 1990 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 133)
- Deane L. Root in the Foster Memorial Library, 1990 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 134)
- Deane L. Root with county commissioner's proclamation of Jan. 13, 1988 as "Stephen Foster Day" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 135)
- Stephen Foster Rose, great-grandson of Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 136)
- Jessie Welch Rose on the steps of the Foster Memorial Home, 1923 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 137)
- Mrs. Joseph D. Stewart, Stephen Foster's landlady (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 138)
- Frances Wells Stuart, 1849 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 139)
- Major Jesse Thorton, father of William and Dunning F. Thorton (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 140)
- John Wanamaker (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 141)
  - John Wanamaker sketch (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 141.01)
  - John Wanamaker (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 141.02)
- Mary B. Wick (as an old woman), mother of Henrietta Crossman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 142)
- Mary B. Wick (as younger woman), mother of Henrietta Crossman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 143)
- Governor Keene Johnson (KY), A.B. "Happy" Chandler (senior), Jim Farley, and Mrs. Chandler singing "My Old Kentucky Home" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 144)
- Evelyn Foster Morneweck visits school, Sept. 7, 1955 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 145)
  - Evelyn Foster Morneweck visits school: photo of Evelyn Foster Morneweck, Alfred Morneweck, and Charlotte Klemm, Sept. 7, 1955 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 145.01)
  - Evelyn Foster Morneweck visits school: Newspaper article about Evelyn Foster Morneweck's visit, Sept. 7, 1955 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 145.02)
- Evelyn and Alfred Morneweck at their 50th anniversary party, 1961 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 146)
- Dear Friends (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 147)
  - Dear Friends: Jim Ferla, Jean Thomas, Deane Root, Kate Young (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 147.01)
  - Framed portrait of Dear Friends: Jean Thomas, Jim Ferla, Deane Root, Kate Thomas (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 147.02)
  - Dear Friends (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 147.03)
  - Dear Friends Logo (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 147.04)
  - Dear Friends (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 147.05)
- Deane Root with Foster's flute before the stained glass windows in the Memorial passageway (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 148)
- Deane Root, Fletcher Hodges, and unidentified others examining Foster's flute at the Memorial (proof sheets) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 149)
  - Deane Root, Fletcher Hodges, and unidentified others examining Foster's flute at the Memorial (proof sheet) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 149.01)
  - Deane Root, Fletcher Hodges, and unidentified others examining Foster's flute at the Memorial (proof sheet) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 149.02)
  - Deane Root, Fletcher Hodges, and unidentified others examining Foster's flute at the Memorial (proof sheet) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 149.03)
- Deane Root and others at the White House Award Ceremony for IMLS, May 18, 1990 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 150)
- Deane L. Root with county commissioners proclamation of Jan. 13, 1988 as "Stephen Foster Day" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 151)
- Deane L. Root with county commissioners proclamation of Jan. 13, 1988 as "Stephen Foster Day" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 152)
- Dorothy Jane Rose and Dallas Clayland Rose on the steps of the Foster Memorial Home (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 153)